submitresume.in 2013-06-30

# Privacy Policy | Jobs In India | Submit Resume

Submit Resume is among leading job search engines India and respects the privacy of its online visitors. In order to protect your trust in us, we have devised our privacy policy such that it allows employers to search for suitable candidates and help job seekers to find jobs from wide range of job listings India in a safe and secured manner. 

Any 'personal identification information' you share with us is protected under our privacy policy. Personal identification information includes any information that reveals your identity such as first and last name, email id, phone number, work place name and physical address.   
Submit Resume does not collect any personal identification information unless you choose to provide it to us. 

**Information Collected**

Submit Resume allows online visitors to browse through the job postings India and other resourceful contents on its website even without requiring the visitors to reveal their personal information. 

On browsing through submitresume.in or using its services, the user explicitly consents to let Submit Resume collect, retain and use any information (a) voluntarily supplied by the users and (b) the information automatically tracked while navigating through the website. 

Log in details of the registered members and uploaded resume (in case of job seekers) are stored safely on the server of Submit Resume. Only under situation of legal obligations, shall Submit Resume access the profile information of its members. 

**Information Use by Submit Resume**

Any information that we collect at the time of registration while searching for employment opportunities is used by Submit Resume for contacting the user whenever we find any record (candidate resume / potential employer) that match the preferences marked by the user in their profile. Also, we may use users’ contact information to reply to their queries, feedback, keep them updated about job openings in India and to make the user-experience better. 

We use email as a way to communicate with our registered members. We reach them by SMS for relevant postings only if they have marked it as their preference. 

**Information Use by employers**

We do not have any control on data use practices of the employers who may view the post resume of job seekers. Even if the candidate seeking job vacancies India voluntarily deletes his/her resume, the employer might have saved the information while it was live and may contact the job seeker. Submit Resume is not liable under such conditions. 

We do not trade, rent or publish any information provided by our online users and registered members to unintended third parties. 

**Links to Other Sites**

Apart from job listings India, Submit Resume has links to third parties such advertisers. Privacy policy of the employing companies and recruitment agencies may have privacy policy differing from ours. We do not have control over the policy for use of information of employers posting job vacancies India, advertisers and other third parties. Submit Resume is not responsible for their data use policies and consequences thereof. 

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

Information tracked while searching job opportunities India or post resume or merely website navigation may be used by our Ad network and other third parties who work to serve you personalize ads and improve your experience on our website. 

Cookies and other tracking technologies automatically records information such as internet domain, internet protocol address, click stream patterns, dates and time website is accessed.   
Users are free to opt in for blocking the cookies or even erasing the cookies. 

**Password Protection**

While searching for jobs in India, job seekers may create a profile with us. Password is the key to your account on Submit Resume and also to the employment opportunities you find here. It is strongly suggested that you keep your log in details to yourself and don’t share it. 

For employers and recruiters, they can post career opportunities India only after successfully registering with Submit Resume. We request you keep your password to yourself and benefit from our services without any security concerns. 

As an established job search engines India, we suggest all our registered members to change their password ones a month. 

**Changes in Privacy Policy**

To make searching jobs in India and talent acquisition safe and secured for our online visitors, Submit Resume makes necessary changes in the privacy policy on continual bases. 

Any changes we make in our privacy policy will be updated here. We request all our online visitors to keep reviewing our privacy statement frequently. 

Should any conflict of interests occur, decision from Submit Resume team shall be final and binding. 

Feel free to [contact here](mailto:help@submitresume.in) if you need anything explained about our privacy policy or have any suggestions to help us make our services better.
